<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="accessibility_ai_identify">Recognise</string>
    <string name="accessibility_color">Colour</string>
    <string name="accessibility_focus_face_pos_mid">Located near the centre of the frame</string>
    <string name="ai_scene_mode_use_hint_text">"Recognise scenes using AI
and adjust preferences automatically"</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_lens_identifies_weak_light">Auxiliary lens is recognising low light</string>
    <string name="center_mark">Centre mark</string>
    <string name="color_effect_entry_blackgold_describe">This high-contrast filter retains only yellow and dark blue colours. Use it on well-lit streets of a night city.</string>
    <string name="color_effect_entry_new_1_describe">A colour scheme commonly used in movies adds green to the darker areas. This filter works well for high-contrast scenes such as dusk in the city.</string>
    <string name="color_effect_entry_new_3_describe">This unique combination of colours works perfect in cloudy weather and soft light.</string>
    <string name="color_enhance_mode">Enhanced colours</string>
    <string name="confirm_location_message">&lt;Data>Welcome to Camera! Tagging your photos and videos with the locations where they are taken will make your Gallery more organised and help you find items faster. Some features might not be available if you restrict adding location info.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>We shall protect your personal information in accordance with the relevant laws, regulations, and privacy policies.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="cta_mimoji_user_links">&lt;Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href =%1$s>User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href =%2$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a> before using this app.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="cta_user_tips">&lt;Data>To fully understand your rights as a user as well as the ways in which we use your data, read and agree to our &lt;a href =%1$s>User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href =%2$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="custom_tint_color_select">Customise colours</string>
    <string name="dolly_zoom_capture_tip2">Keep your subject in the centre and move the device away steadily</string>
    <string name="dolly_zoom_capture_tip6">Move your subject to the centre of the frame</string>
    <string name="dolly_zoom_guide_tip2">Try to avoid large areas of solid colour.</string>
    <string name="download_automatic_message_cn">Download feature plug-ins automatically when this device is connected to WLAN?</string>
    <string name="download_automatic_summary_cn">Download feature plug-ins automatically over WLAN</string>
    <string name="download_hint_check_on_wifi_cn">"You're connected to WLAN. Download this %1$s MB file now?"</string>
    <string name="download_hint_cn">"Looks like your device isn't connected to WLAN. Use %1$s MB of mobile data to download items now?"</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_month_day">M-d</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_year_month">M-yyyy</string>
    <string name="fmt_date_numeric_year_month_day">M-d-yyyy</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour">"H 'o''clock'"</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute">H:mm</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute_second">H:mm:ss</string>
    <string name="fmt_time_24hour_minute_second_millis">H:mm:ss.S</string>
    <string name="mimoji_detect_haircolor_failed">"Couldn't detect hair colour"</string>
    <string name="mimoji_detect_skincolor_failed">"Couldn't detect skin colour"</string>
    <string name="network_access_user_notice_message_live_video">"&lt;Data>Camera needs to connect to the internet to provide effects, music, and other features for short videos.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>By tapping \"Agree\" below, you're agreeing to our &lt;a href =%1$s>User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href =%2$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>, and allowing Camera to connect to the internet.&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="network_access_user_notice_message_mi_live_video">&lt;Data>Welcome to short videos! Our service needs to connect to the network to provide you with music and other features. &lt;br/>&lt;br/>Before using our service, you need to read and agree to our &lt;a href =%1$s>User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href =%2$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>, as well as allow the app to connect to the internet.&lt;/Data></string>
    <string name="network_access_user_notice_message_sticker">"&lt;Data>Camera needs to connect to the internet to provide stickers for this feature.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>By tapping \"Agree\" below, you're agreeing to our &lt;a href =%1$s>User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href =%2$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>, and allowing Camera to connect to the internet.&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="network_access_user_notice_message_voice_caption">"&lt;Data>Camera needs to connect to the internet to provide speech-to-text output functionality.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>By tapping \"Agree\" below, you're agreeing to our &lt;a href =%1$s>User Agreement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href =%2$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a>, and allowing Camera to connect to the internet.&lt;/Data>"</string>
    <string name="network_connection_prerequisites">Turn on Bluetooth and Wi-Fi in Control centre to be able to use Dual phone recording.</string>
    <string name="network_connection_prerequisites_china">Turn on Bluetooth and WLAN in Control center to be able to use Dual phone recording.</string>
    <string name="new_bie_dialog_cancel">Close feature description</string>
    <string name="new_bie_dialog_desc">Feature description</string>
    <string name="parameter_manual_picturestyle_description">Saturation allows you to control the depth and intensity of colours, adjusting contrast brings out or minimises the difference between light and dark, and sharpness renders the details along the outlines.</string>
    <string name="parameter_metering_description">Average metering takes into account all areas of your image, working best for evenly lit scenes. Centre-weighted metering mainly focuses on the central area of the frame and gives due consideration to the brightness of the surrounding area, which is suitable for shooting subjects in the centre of the frame. Spot metering only covers the area in one spot, giving you precise control over the exposure.</string>
    <string name="pref_camera_autoexposure_entry_centerweighted">Centre weighted</string>
    <string name="pref_camera_coloreffect_entry_instagram_clarendon">Colour focus</string>
    <string name="pref_camera_movie_solid_title">Image stabilisation</string>
    <string name="pref_camera_predictive_shutter_description">Track motion to minimise blur on the photos of children, pets, and other active subjects</string>
    <string name="pref_custom_tint_title">Colours</string>
    <string name="pref_customization_title">Customise</string>
    <string name="pref_cv_watermark_summary">"Previews are provided for your reference only. Leica watermark will appear on JPEG and HEIF photos. Burst shots, Ultra HD, and Fun Cam images aren't supported."</string>
    <string name="pref_hdr10_hdr10plus_video_mode_description">Record high resolution videos in HDR10+/HDR10 to optimise colours and dynamic range. Recorded videos can be played only on HDR10+/HDR10 compatible devices.</string>
    <string name="pref_hybrid_video_mode_description">Use HLG technology to enhance colours and dynamic range of the videos recorded in high resolution</string>
    <string name="pref_true_colour_video_mode_description">Record videos with Dolby Vision to capture lifelike details, stunning colours, and striking contrast (this feature might not be compatible with some third party apps)</string>
    <string name="preference_copied">"'%1$s' copied to clipboard."</string>
    <string name="pro_color_mode">Pro colour</string>
    <string name="remote_online_guide">Turn on Dual phone recording on the other device using the Control centre toggle.</string>
    <string name="remote_online_introduction_ii">To make this feature work, the other Mi or Redmi device must support Dual phone recording. It can be turned on using the Control centre toggle.</string>
    <string name="super_night_hint">Optimising image… Keep your device stable.</string>
    <string name="time_stamp_date_format">dd/MM/yyyy</string>
    <string name="timefreeze_guide_tip3">Ask your subject to stay in the centre of the frame.</string>
    <string name="user_notice_identify_summary_format">Before using Camera, you must agree to our <a href="http://www.miui.com/res/doc/eula.html?lang=en_US">User Agreement</a> and <a href="http://www.miui.com/res/doc/privacy.html?lang=en_US">Privacy Policy</a>. Camera also needs to connect to the internet to work normally. Agree?</string>
    <string name="video_bokeh_color_point">Colour spots</string>
    <string name="video_effect_entry_color_retention">Colour focus</string>
    <string name="video_effect_entry_color_retention_describe">This portrait filter shows people in colour, making backgrounds black and white.</string>
    <string name="video_effect_entry_meet_describe">Soft colours recreate the nostalgic look of the movies shot on film.</string>
    <string name="video_prompter_shrink_description">Minimise</string>
</resources>
